A Guide to the University Relations, General Correspondence File of Bevin Alexander, Director of Information Services, 1965-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University Relations, General Correspondence File of Bevin Alexander, Director of Information Services 1965-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/1.671
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1977 April 2.
Contents List
- Advertising 1966 Feb 14 (Box 1)
- Alumni News 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- Chamber of Commerce 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 1)
- Colleges and Universities 1965 Jul-1966 Jun (Box 1)
- Community Colleges 1965 August (Box 1)
- Garden Club of Virginia 1965 Oct 15-1966 Apr (Box 1)
- George Mason College 1965 Jan (Box 1)
- Information Requested 1965 Jun-1966 May (Box 1)
- Magazines 1965 Jul-Sep (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous 1965 Aug-1966 Jun (Box 1)
- Motion Picture 1965 Mar-1966 May (Box 1)
- Newspapers (local) 1966 Jan-May (Box 1)
- Newspapers (state & national) 1965 Jul-1966 Jul (Box 1)
- Photos Requested 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 1)
- Photographers 1965 Jun-Dec (Box 1)
- Photos that have been Received 1965 Aug-1966 Jun (Box 1)
- Press Services 1966 Apr 25 (Box 1)
- Printing (empty folder) n.d. (Box 1)
- Publications (U.Va. Student) 1965 Aug-Sep (Box 1)
- Questionnaires 1965 Jun 19 (Box 1)
- Radio Stations 1965 Jul-1966 Feb (Box 1)
- Special Releases 1965 Jun-Aug (Box 1)
- Television 1965 Sep-1966 Mar (Box 1)
- Tours (folder empty) n.d. (Box 1)
- United States Information Agency 1966 May (Box 1)
- Virginia Press Association 1966 Feb-1966 Jun (Box 1)
- William Byrd Press 1965 Jun-1966 Jan (Box 1)